[ED]
Thank you for watching!
How is the first day of the event going?
Right now, about 80% of me is nervous, and the remaining 20% wants to have a lot of fun.
But for the show, I want to know how fun it is to perform live, so let's have fun together!
I'm already looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm even more excited about it now that I've recently completed my "Shukubou" compulsion!
I'm going to do my best and let my hair fly!
Let's make idol dancing our dream
Make it to the top
We love, we love
♪ We love, we love
♪ Right now, and now, and now
Yuka, can you make it?
Um, Mamiri, you were off... by 2.5, I think.
So, I was a little off.
Please.
Please take care of it.
Thank you very much.
Then we're good to go.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you very much.
Rehearsal is over.
We're done.
Thank you very much.
It was fun.
I'll do my best.
I have to change quickly.
I'm so nervous.
Um...
I made a mistake in one of the formations.
I made a mistake.
That part...
I'm sorry.I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Oh, it's heavy.
Highlights.
It's a self highlight.
It looks great.
Does it make my nose look taller?
It looks good.
I'm going for it.
This is your first time in front of an audience, right? Live?
Yes, it is.
Well, yes.
I'm a little nervous. I think my heart is going to skip a beat.
Liar.
Oh, no.
Don't be a meth-head.
Oh, they're pickles.
We're gonna run out of food.
I've already had two.
He said he already ate one.
Eat it after you've eaten it.
No, eat it.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy!
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
He's being bullied by a younger man.
It's hot.
Oh, you want some Pirari?
No, the lip is a little out of place.
Come on, guys.
Hey.
Stop making that face.
It's good.
It's delicious.It's delicious.
It's delicious.
It's so delicious.
It's like a sugar coating.
It's delicious!
Better than Aoi's food report!
Aoi's food report just now.
Himari took it away.
It was in a miserable state.
Is it good?
Can I express it with my expression?
I'll take it.
There's a delicious look on your face.
What's that? Huh?
Yummy.
I don't know if I'm going to make it to the commercial.
He's good with chocolate, too.
Oh, my God.
It smells so good.
I'm doing my makeup.
Look at this.
I got bit by a dog.
If you get too close to my hand, it hurts.
So be careful.
I'm going to be on the show!
[Hajime Shacho's ending]
I've been in a big hurry since a while ago.
I'm feeling really scattered.
I'm going to do my best to stay calm on stage and have fun!
The first time there are six of us!
Well, there's only 10 minutes left...
I'm so nervous.
Well, I'm off!
I'll wait for a moment and then I'll calm down.
I'll do my best to be instant clean.I'll do my best for instant cleanliness.
Which one is it? I haven't decided on the Kaigomi yet.
Please let me wait for one more hour.
I will do my very best, thank you very much.
I'll do my best to do the best I can do.
Bye bye!
I'm going to give it my all until the end on the first day of the releve!
Wooooooo!
I'm still fighting.
Have fun! Good luck!
I'll do my best!
Have fun! I'll do my best!
What do we do?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Something's wrong, guys.
It's safe. It's safe.
I'm serious. Stay out of this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
You look like a real Temodar!
I'm sorry if I'm this strong.
I'm turned on.
Are you sure you're okay?
Please don't stop, seriously.
I'm trying to do my best, but I'm trying to do my best.
Wait a minute.
I just want to do it when it's done.
The person who based it on you is crying.
Thank you for watching
■Blast illustration forts
ichen
Juice-Juice
So, the first full albumSo, the first full album
MOMENT Release Commemorative Event Day 1 Osaka has begun!
And so, two new members are making their first appearances!
I'm Yulia, the newest member of BTG. I'm Yulia, the newest member of BTG, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm Hiroyu, also a new member of BTG. I'm Hiroyu, also a new member of BTG, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
This will be the first time for all six of us to perform together on stage, so I'm really excited,
How are you feeling? How are you feeling right now?
I'm so nervous, and I'm still nervous,
I'm still nervous, but I'm going to do my best, making the most of what I've learned from the other members.
You seem very passionate.
Why is that good?
How about Julia?
Right now I am not nervous at all, the opposite of you,
It's my first time in Oita, so I don't know what will happen,
I'm not sure how it will turn out, but I'll do the best I can and have fun. I hope you will enjoy it as much as you can.
I will do my best for Juice from now on as well.
Our first event as six members ended successfully!
Thanks for your hard work!
It was the first time for the six of you. How was it? Weren't you really nervous?
I was so nervous. I really had a stomach ache.
I almost cried a little like Aoi's face.
Did I make you cry?
It wasn't my fault.
I was just that nervous.
I was really nervous.
I had never seen Ilaria and Hilary before, right?
I'm having so much fun.
It was so much fun.
It was too much fun.
Everything was fun.
Everything, everything, everything was fun.
Hillary was so relaxed that she made me feel at ease.
I have another event next week, and this summer, I'll be at a lot of events.
Let's do our best to grow up with a good insight into child-rearing.
Let's work hard this summer!
Power!Power!
Hey!